Day three already... it's going so fast.
Yeah.
Sure you're not tired, Nono-pi?
I'll be fine since we're not cosplaying today.
I'm just here for Senpai.
As long as you're all okay.
Okay, Okumura.
I'm busy on Day Three,
so I won't be joining you,
but as the Cosplay Club advisor,
I need to give you a word of advice.
We're the Manga Club, Sensei.
If you're going,
there's one cosplayer you have to go see.
Really?
Right! I wanted to get a copy of her cosrom.
Okay, let's go! Where to first?
If Sensei was that insistent, she's gotta be big...
Wait, Senpai, is that the same hat?
Nope, the one Sensei signed
is too precious to wear now!
I'm wearing the extra one I bought just in case.
Didn't he say they only made ten of those?
Wait, Aria-chan,
I thought you were supposed to visit family today.
Yeah, that was the plan,
but we're going tomorrow instead.
You got old.
C'mon, let's go! Ririsa's got stuff to buy!
Okay!
This Wonderful World
Hey there, Liliel gang!
I heard about what happened.
Great job yesterday!
Thank you so much!
Can I get your new cosrom, please?
Of course! This one's for all ages.
Oh, you don't need to pay.
Huh?
Ogino, that's 2000 yen.
I take it I'll be purchasing it for you, then?
Just get me a copy of your new cosrom.
We'll call it a trade!
Sounds great!
Hi, Liliel-chan! Long time no see!
I saw you online! So glad you're okay.
Thanks! Sorry to cause so much drama.
Can I buy your new cosrom?
That'll be 2000 yen for the full set.
I'm busy on Day Three. I'm busy on Day Three.
Sensei?
Hey, I'm on a date!
This is my day off, so who cares?!
Can't say no to a date, right?
Eri needed help at the booth, okay?
Sorry, kids, but I get to play with Mayuri-sensei today.
Don't make it sound dirty!
After this, we're going to that one café
that has god-tier service just for Comiket,
then a karaoke after party,
then a cosplay rave.
Nothing dirty happening here!
Mayuri, these kids won't know what a cosplay rave is.
Oh, right.
The cosrom you're looking for is over at that booth.
There's no line right now.
Really?
Is that the cosplayer you
wanted to see, Ririsa-chan?
Yeah!
She spends a whole year making her
costume and sculpting her body for a character,
so we only see her once
a year at Summer Comiket.
Five-star rarity, then.
If Ririsa's this excited...
Then what's she like?
One copy of your newest release!
Okay!
plain girls with glasses RULE
That'll be 5000 yen for the set.
I like the costume, but what cosplay is that?
Oh, I'm just helping out!
She's up on the roof getting photos taken right now.
Well, well!
If it isn't Liliel!
You're Nyaru-chan from NekoConnect!
Are you just getting finished with photos?
Yup, sorry!
But, I wouldn't mind sticking around
if Kai-sama wanted a few shots!
I'm good.
Things are chaotic enough up here as it is.
That's so something the broody
Kai-sama would've said at the start of his arc!
That's okay.
I gotta play the game right and keep
talking to him every time he shows up!
Who is she?!
And why is she looking at him like that?!
I'll show her!
Everyone's such good friends.
Hey, that's her new cosrom.
Y-yeah.
You can find her beyond that crowd over there.
Though my crowd was totally bigger than hers!
I mean...
She doesn't care that much about
drawing big crowds or selling tons of cosroms.
She's just dedicated...
...to the art of cosplay.
Hey, Mayura.
Were you guys talking about the Heavenly Queen?
Yeah.
I want Ririsa and the gang to see
her as what they should aspire towards.
Because she's not interested in popularity.
She's all about defining cosplay as an art form.
Erika-chan!
Photographers might think Nagomi's
the best cosplayer out there...
But, cosplayers would choose her instead.
She's the closest anyone's gotten to being truly 2D.
Heavenly Queen Erika Awayuki.
Wow.
The costume, the wig, the details and props,
even the shape of her body,
everything is a perfect replica of the original!
I didn't think this precision was humanly possible!
I put tons of work into being the best Liliel,
but I'm nowhere close to looking like the original!
Liliel's arms and waist are way slimmer,
and her boobs are bigger!
Well, yeah...
I'm not even close.
How do I get to her level?!
I can't believe I thought I looked good!
I still have so much more to improve upon!
You're already really good.
will suffer collateral damage
Comic Market 99 Circle Application
I got our application form for Winter Comiket!
I'm gonna put together a cosrom and sell it there!
I can't wait to do this again with you!
You already got what you came for, huh?
You don't really have a reason to keep cosplaying.
I guess that's true.
But, is that what you want, Nono-pi?
For me to stop cosplaying with you?
Huh?! I mean, why ask me...
Guess I'm done, then.
Wait, no!
You told Ririsa how you feel. Now tell me.
I...
I don't want you to stop!
I thought we were friends!
Ririsa.
I'm not gonna stop.
Not when I had so much fun cosplaying with you guys!
Yay!
I can't wait to cosplay with you again, Aria-chan!
No fair!
You were gonna keep cosplaying
no matter what I said!
You're not getting rid of me yet, Nono-pi!
We're stuck together forever!
Like I care!
It's from Mom.
Remember this place?
So your parents are cool?
Yeah. Oh, and Dad made his deadline.
I can't thank you guys enough!
Please, it was mostly Senpai!
Yeah.
The manga you made,
the manga you created, made me happy!
I couldn't have done it without you, Okumura.
Thank you.
Y-you're welcome.
Don't tell me I've got even more competition!
I'm so glad we're all such good friends.
Okay, who's ready for Day Four tomorrow?!
I have work!
I'm out of town.
Could I please sleep in, Ririsa-chan?
Good morning, Senpai!
H-hey.
Just me and Ririsa today.
Reminds me of the first time we went to an event.
I can't believe it's the last day!
Yeah.
It's been a while since it's been just the two of us, huh?
Oh, y-yeah, huh.
Hey, we're on a date!
Wait, this is totally a Comiket date!
Why does my heart start racing
whenever I'm alone with him?
I mean, I love Senpai, but not like that!
He's just a friend!
Look, it'll be fine.
Our first event felt like a date,
but we got through it.
No need to freak out.
Wait, what's with the suitcase?
Oh! I brought something to
change into once we get there.
Huh?
Thanks for waiting!
Ever since my first Comiket,
I've wanted to shop the floor in costume!
I didn't have the courage to do it alone,
but with you, I thought...
Oh, I'm in trouble.
Look, Liliel!
Wait, is that the one cosplayer?
Wait, Liliel...
Aren't people going to think we're like, together?
Cosplayers can have boyfriends! We're not idols.
Wow. I didn't expect you to have
an immediate counter for that.
I mean...
I kinda wouldn't mind if people
thought we were together.
What the hell is that supposed to mean, Liliel?!
Still...
I thought that might weird you out.
No, it's totally fine...
So I brought this for you!
Liliel... When did you make this?
I knew you'd make a great Ashford-sama!
You could totally be the next Heavenly King!
I'll pass, thanks.
Their costumes are so good!
Look, Ash and Liliel!
You're right. We're not a couple,
we're just a cosplay group.
That'll make walking around less awkward!
Can I buy a copy?
Of course! That'll be 800 yen.
I knew when I got back into
AshLili that it's pretty obscure now,
but I thought I'd sell at least one copy...
I should've just done something for
Hellmaids like everyone else...
Excuse me!
Might I take a look through your book?
Y-y-yeah, sure!
AAAAAAAAAAAAAA
Liliel and Ash-sama!
Here, in the flesh, at my booth!
They're so freaking cute! Is this real life?!
Oh, look, Ash-sama!
Tales of our adventures sure have traveled far!
I did not expect to find a
picture book exposition here.
Always interesting, these port towns.
They're in character on an adventure!
This book tells the story of our romance.
Oh, goodness.
And they're totally flirting! I love them so much!
May I have a copy?
One for me too, madam.
Of course! It's free for you!
It's all right, we'll pay!
Please, don't!
I mean, I saw a Liliel cosplay, uh,
a photo of you, online back in May.
And that's what inspired me to draw this.
I did it for the fandom, you know?
So you don't need to pay.
Consider this a trade.
Thank you so much!
I felt so connected with the Liliel fandom today!
Me too.
Everyone was so happy to see Liliel.
Wait, really?!
Yeah.
Most of the time, we're either studying for school,
or geeking out about anime and manga.
It's not every day we get the opportunity
to make other people happy like you did.
You're amazing,
Ririsa.
Oh, sorry! It felt right in the moment,
I just didn't think!
It's okay!
Y-you're amazing, Senpai.
I just cosplay because I think it's cool.
You're the one who accepted
me without any judgment.
And I only started cosplaying because of you.
Together, we'll make it happen!
I made my first cosrom because of you.
I'll be there for you!
When I was about to give up,
you gave me the strength to keep going.
I'd be nothing without you.
You're the reason I'm so amazing. It's you.
I can't help it. I love him so much.
Is it because he's Ash-sama right now?
I can't think of him like this.
Maybe I don't like him as just a friend.
Maybe it's...
Lo...
Hey!
You dropped part of your costume!
Wait, is this yours?
No, I have mine.
Thank you!
Ashford-sama?
Liliel?
One moment, please!
This is my first time in Japan.
This is my first time...
MUMBLE MUMBLE
Okay!
My name is Xiaoyu! I'm a cosplayer,
and this is my first time in Japan!
You came all the way here?!
Lots of people travel to come to Comiket!
It's famous!
And we all love Japanese manga!
I'm so excited! I've never met another Liliel fan!
I'm excited, too!
It's so cool that Liliel has fans outside Japan, too!
This is the Side Story outfit! It's so cute.
I love the bare shoulders!
I love the thicker material on her original outfit!
Did you make it yourself?
Yes, I did!
The joy of finding a fellow otaku
crosses all languages and borders.
This is a once-in-a-lifetime chance!
Can we take some pictures together?!
Absolutely!
Wouldn't that be against canon, Ririsa?
There's never two Liliels.
You're right, that's never happened in canon!
What do you think?
Two Liliels will make some really fun photos!
Let's do it!
Ririsa?
The other day, I got so caught up with
staying in character that I passed out.
But, the whole reason I like staying in
character is because that's more fun for me.
I'm not going to be a stickler if it ruins that fun!
It's not worth it if it makes me miss
out on a once-in-a-lifetime chance!
Let's go, Xiaoyu-chan!
Okay, then let's go up to the photo area!
Cool. I'll go do my own thing.
You have to come with us, Ashford-sama!
Huh?
Boy, that takes me back! Lord Ashford and...
Two Liliels?
That's that one Liliel.
Wow, you're famous!
Liliel-chan!
Everyone rushed in to get pictures!
Never guessed I'd be doing this today...
But, refusing would be an insult to Liliel.
Senpai's into it!
Someone here taught me that cosplay
is nothing to be embarrassed about.
Ash-sama and Liliel would totally go like this!
S-senpai's with another Liliel?!
Why does it feel so wrong?!
Ririsa?!
Wait, is she jealous?!
Are you jealous, Ririsa?!
Are the two Liliels fighting over Ash?
Did that ever happen in the manga?
That's a bit out of character.
It's a deep cut.
It must be a metaphor for how Liliel feels
torn between duty and her love for Ash.
One's wearing her original costume,
the other is wearing her spin-off costume.
Never have I seen such an advanced
expression of fandom through cosplay!
That's so smart.
That's gotta be it.
That's our Liliel!
Stellar work.
Thank you! I had so much fun today!
Same here!
You helped me learn something
new about myself, too!
Could I get a few photos with you, too?
Senpai, you seem kinda
worked up about Xiaoyu's Liliel.
What?!
No, I'm just nervous! I get shy with strangers!
I know you, so I'm comfortable with you, and...
You're the only Liliel for me!
W-what's that supposed to mean?
I have no idea.
Sorry! Don't worry, I won't steal your boyfriend.
No, that's not what I meant!
And he's not my boyfriend!
Here, get together, I'll take a picture!
Huh?
Closer, c'mon!
You're the cutest couple in all of Japan!
I have to go now.
Thanks so much for today! I'll never forget you!
Same here.
I hope we'll see you again at another event!
Sorry, I can't promise you will.
Huh?
I don't know when I'll be able to come to Japan again.
This country is wonderful.
Everyone can make amazing manga!
Nothing is off-limits!
Take care of Liliel.
And please take care...
...of this wonderful world.
I can't believe Comiket's over.
She's all fired up!
Oh, just...
You put so much energy into
everything for this Comiket.
I was a little worried you'd be
completely drained by the end.
No way!
I'm not gonna waste
a single day from here on out!
The moment I get home,
I'm gonna start brainstorming my next cosplay!
Yeah, sounds good.
My waifu is 2D.
I'm not interested in 3D girls.
But...
2.5D might be okay.
I'm not in love!
I am definitely not in love with her!
But before I realized it,
I had fallen in love with this wonderful world.
Manga Club On the Beach